[Music]
[Applause]
hey YouTube Dan here from EAP films
official and welcome to the next video
today and it is manual life Philippines
commercial
2017 now I don't know what this is other
than a commercial so we're back on to
the commercial theme for today uh or at
least for now um
I have there's no thumbnails to to to
check on so far so let's jump straight
in and see what the fuss is about I'm
imagining this is going to be quite an
upsetting commercial uh just given the
type of commercials you guys seem to
want me to react to so we'll just see
what happens I don't have any tissues
available either so I should have been
more
prepared just in case you never
know good evening s l
[Music]
but I used to be a banker it was my
dream
job because I was always dreaming in my
[Music]
job
fore
friends now I'm a full-time standup
comedian by
choice my
[Music]
bosses I want to be a stand
[Applause]
and when people see my family they say
wow your family is complete you have
doctors attorneys and a stand-up
comedian so you have a doctor's
appointment an attorney's appointment
and a
disappointment this is actually quite
[Music]
good
so no no no no no oh no
[Music]
no thanks for everything
dad
[Music]
Jesus oh my
God I thought that was I was just about
to start well I have already started
leaking in my eyes I genuinely thought
that was going to go in another
direction oh if it's Jolly B that's how
it would have ended as well and just
leave you with your heart RI out I'm so
glad that he came back at the end of
there oh
man that wasn't even that emotional I
don't think until until that point I
thought I think it was building up the
the support I always find with adverts
like that the ones that affected the
most are the ones that I think
um earn the most respect and I think by
that I don't mean like what I mean is if
that Dad was supportive and laughing at
all the jokes and
stuff then you know it would have been
okay okay but because he was quite Stern
and perhaps didn't find them funny the
the comedian was always trying to make
you know do the most to make his dad
proud
and it was almost like whil he did
support him and he did uh you know I
suppose have his own way of appreciating
what his son did just the fact that when
he when he wasn't sat there it was
almost like he didn't he had a lot of
respect for
him and cared what he thought about him
um and when he wasn't there it was
almost like it was almost too late to
say anything uh so I think that's what
it was it was it was a respect for his
father well mutual respect I guess and
it was just oh I'm so glad that his dad
appeared at the end there cuz that could
have been a whole lot
of a whole lot of more feels I think my
God I'm terrible and also so I think
partly cuz my
dad I haven't seen my dad
in nearly a year haven't spoke to him
probably since last year
um which is weird because I'd say we're
pretty close in in that we you know when
I do see him and stuff we always get on
we always have a drink together and
stuff but we've never been close in that
we've always you know see each other all
the time ring each other every single
week and that and I suppose in some
respects it's from me this has kind of
brought a bit of a personal touch to it
because you know I love my dad and I
haven't seen him in so long but I know
he's there and one day he's not going to
be and I don't know when it's going to
be hopefully not for a long time but you
know life happens I mean look at the
recent attacks in Manchester if you've
heard about that on the news you know
children have been injured been killed
and just by some idiot with a with a
bomb and I suppose you know when you
think you have your whole life ahead of
you you just don't know when that's
going to come to an end and we must take
it each day as it comes and always you
know tell those we love that we love
them God that was
deep anyway so I let you think on that
so thanks for watching I hope you
enjoyed my reaction don't forget to like
share And subscribe and we'll see you
next time
[Music]